http://www.nuvo.net/site/terms.html

Writers
Terms & AgreementsThese Terms of Use apply to all websites maintained, owned and operated by NUVO Cultural Foundation, including, but not limited to, nuvo.net. Restrictions on Use of WebsiteThis website ("Website") is owned and operated by NUVO Cultural Foundation ("NUVO"). By accessing or using or registering on this Website, you agree to be bound by and comply with these Terms of Use. If you do not agree with these Terms of Use, then do not use this Website. NUVO has the right, in its discretion, to modify or update these Terms of Use at any time without notice. You agree to review this agreement periodically since any use of this Website following any such change will constitute your acceptance of the modifications. NUVO Comments PolicyComments are welcomed and encouraged on this site, but there are some instances in which comments will be deleted as follows:Comments deemed to be spam or questionable spam will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted, but comments should be pertinent to the post topic.Comments including profanity may be deleted.Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive may be deleted.Comments that attack a person individually will be deleted.Comments that violate a person’s privacy will be deleted.We reserve the right to delete any comments submitted without notice. We further reserve the right to disable comments on the site at any time. This comment policy is subject to change at any time. Use of MaterialsThis Website, and the information, content and materials displayed on or used in connection with the Website, including all text, articles, editorials, advertising, images, photographs, audio, video, classifieds, computer code and software (collectively, the "Content"), is the property of NUVO and its affiliates and licensors. You may not use any of the Content except as provided in these Terms of Use. Any copying, rearrangement, redistribution, modification, use or publication by you of any Content or any part of the Website, except for the limited rights of use granted hereunder, is strictly prohibited.You may use the Content online and for your non-commercial, personal use only. Copying these materials for anything other than your personal use is a violation of copyright and trademark laws. You may not distribute any Content or make copies of it available to anyone else, whether or not for payment or other consideration. You may not create any derivative works from any Content or remove any trademark, copyright or other notice from any Content. You may not otherwise modify, copy, frame, reproduce, sell, publish, transmit, display or otherwise use any Content or any portion of the Website without the prior written permission of NUVO.Requests to use the Content for any purpose other than as permitted in these Terms of Use should be directed to editors@nuvo.net.The trademarks, logos and service marks displayed on this Website are owned by NUVO and other third party providers. For example, NUVO and nuvo.net are trademarks owned by NUVO Cultural Foundation. No trademarks on this Website may be used without the prior written permission of NUVO. Registration and Account CreationNUVO may require that you register and set up an account to use certain portions of the Website and/or the Website in its entirety. In order to do so, you may be provided or required to choose a password and username, and you may need to provide your name, your gender, your email, your date of birth, your zip code, and/or other registration information (collectively, "Registration Information"). You agree and represent that all Registration Information provided by you to Website is accurate and current. You may not impersonate another person when registering and setting up an account on the Website. If your Registration Information changes, you must promptly update it on the Website using the appropriate mechanism, if available. If you have questions about your personal information, please see our Privacy Policy.You will be solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Registration Information if you register and set up an account on the Website. You may not: (a) authorize others to use your Registration Information; or (b) sub-license, transfer, sell or assign your Registration Information to any third party without our written approval and any attempt to do so will be null and void and shall be considered a material breach of this Terms of Use. You are solely responsible for: (a) all use or activity on your account including without limitation use of the account by any person who, with or without your permission, uses your Registration Information or who has access to any computer on which your Registration Information is accessible. If you have a reason to believe that your account is no longer secure (i.e. in the event of loss, theft or unauthorized disclosure or use of Registration Information or credit card information stored on the Website), you must promptly change the applicable Registration Information on the Website using the appropriate mechanism, if available. User ConductNUVO is not responsible for materials submitted or posted to any of its Websites or Social Media accounts, including user-submitted blog posts, comments, letters to the editor, classified advertisements  and reviews. NUVO does not and cannot monitor all materials posted or transmitted by users. NUVO and its designees have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any areas involving user participation, and to edit, refuse to post or remove any content submitted by any user for any reason whatsoever in its discretion.Do not post any personal information that you do want to be accessed by the general public. NUVO is not responsible for unsolicited communications that may arise from your posting information on this Website.You agree that you shall not upload, transmit, distribute or otherwise publish through this Website or NUVO, Inc. Social Media accounts any content that: a) is libelous or defamatory or tends to mislead or reflect unfairly on any person, business or entity; b) is obscene, indecent, pornographic, inflammatory, abusive or threatening or otherwise expresses bigotry or racism; c) violates, plagiarizes or infringes any rights of any entity or person, including copyrights, trademarks, patents, rights of publicity or privacy or any other proprietary rights; d) violates any law; e) constitutes or advocates illegal or violent activity; f) advertises or otherwise solicits funds or is a solicitation for goods or services; or g) contains a virus or other harmful or disruptive component. You agree that you will not in any way interfere with the delivery or display of advertisements appearing on the Website. You further agree that you: (a) will not disrupt, attack, overwhelm, modify, reverse engineer, decrypt or interfere with the Website or its associated software, hardware and/or servers in any way; (b) will not impede or interfere with others’ use of the Website; (c) other than connecting to NUVO’s servers by http requests using a web browser, will not attempt to gain access to NUVO’s servers by any means – including without limitation by using administrator passwords or by masquerading as an administrator while using the Website; and (d) will not impersonate any person or entity or misrepresent your identity.Any violation of the foregoing may result in restrictions on your access to the Website and may be referred to law enforcement authorities. NUVO reserves the right to disclose information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or government request. NUVO and its affiliates shall have no liability for any action or inaction by them in respect of any conduct relating to materials submitted or posted by users. License for Submitted ContentYou agree that by posting content (including classified ads), sending emails, inputting data, answering questions, uploading data or files or otherwise communicating with NUVO, you are granting to NUVO and its affiliates a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, unrestricted right and license to use, publish, display, modify, distribute, reproduce and create derivative works from these materials as NUVO sees fit in any form, media or technology now known or later developed, and that you shall have no claims against NUVO for using these materials. You also grant NUVO and the affiliates the right to use your name and other information you provide in connection with their use of materials you submit to the Website. NUVO is free to use any ideas, concepts or know-how contained in any user-submitted material for any purpose whatsoever, including the development of products and services using such information. You represent and warrant that you have all the necessary rights in and to any material you submit and the material does not infringe or violate the rights of any third party. Personally Identifiable InformationNUVO will not sell or share any of your personal information to a third party. NUVO will gather personally identifiable information about you only when you provide it voluntarily for specific purposes such as posting an ad or signing up for an e-mail newsletter.To see what folks like and don't like on our site, we track how our visitors use nuvo.net. We may also collect your personal information from your registering for contests, surveys and newsletters; this can include contests, surveys and newsletters. We won't, though, release your e-mail address or name or any other personal information to anyone else outside NUVO unless we have your consent - or, in those rare cases when we are under a legal order to do so, or there's an emergency involving danger to a person or property. So, in other words, we won't provide our advertisers or anyone else outside NUVO with any of your information specifically unless you've given us your consent to do so. If you do choose to provide your personally identifiable information for the purposes of a third-party survey, contest, or newsletter, your consent shall be deemed to be given for the release of your personally identifiable information with regard to that third party only, in addition to NUVO. The NUVO employees or consultants allowed access to personal information about you are ONLY those who need to have access. Any employee or consultant who violates these policies is subject to possible termination or prosecution – or other disciplinary action.Sometimes, third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates, and joint ventures perform functions on our behalf, such as shipping or stocking orders, credit card processing, providing customer service, etc. These third party entities are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of this personal information. They can't use or alter this data in any way other than to provide the Site's requested services. Cookies"Cookies" is the term for the small text files that allow Web sites to store and retrieve information about you from your computer system. NUVO in fact does serve cookies to track individual site usage - but we don't use cookies to retrieve any information from your computer - other than the information originally sent in a NUVO cookie (for example, a user code). As for how our advertisers use cookies that originate from their Web site, we have had no control over that. You can always decline our cookies - if your browser permits, but our site's features may become limited to you, and so we'd recommend that you leave them turned on.It's a fact that all computers and servers on the Internet use IP addresses to recognize and communicate with each other. NUVO collects IP addresses to figure out, for example, how many visitors we have, so we analyze our site to retrieve aggregate, non-personal information. When you access our site, our servers enter the IP address of that computer into a log. However, to maintain our users' anonymity, we do not associate IP addresses with records containing personal information.We will not use cookies or IP address tracking to retrieve any personal information from your computer. Communications from UsOccasionally, we send you info, announcements or updates about the site, NUVO or our partners. If you don't like it you can terminate these newsletters, subscriptions, contest results, survey inquiries, etc. with a simple "opt out" procedure. All you need to do use the "unsubscribe" function or link, or email editors@nuvo.net, and we'll remove your name from that mailing list. Giveaways and ContestsWhen it comes to giveaways or contests on our site, if you sign up to be eligible, your info will be shared with the advertiser or sponsor of that giveaway or contest - BUT ONLY for one-time use to notify you if you have won. The giveaway or contest may have its own terms that in fact conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy; if so, the terms of the giveaway or contest shall govern. Note that personally identifiable information will be collected ONLY if you voluntarily submit it to us or our sponsors. Unless you've given us permission, we will not use your personally identifiable information for any purpose other than the administration of the contest or giveaway.ChildrenChildren under the age of 13 should not use this site. We don't target our site toward children under the age of 13 nor can we screen them from using the site. Some of NUVO's material on this site is for mature audiences, and parents and guardians should take responsibility for monitoring their children's use. NUVO doesn't collect or distribute information that indicates whether a user is a child. Links to Third-Party SitesNUVO is not responsible, nor shall it be held liable for, the content, services or products provided on third-party websites, nor for the practices of any third party.  We are an e-family: we provide links and pointers to Web sites maintained by other organizations. We do this as a convenience to users, but we don't control, operate, or endorse such sites. We also disclaim any responsibility for info on those sites and any products or services they offer; and, of course, we cannot vouch for their privacy policies. In addition, we don't make any representations or warranties that any linked sites (or even OUR site) will function without error or interruption, that any defects will be corrected, or that these sites and their servers are free of problems that could harm your computer, including viruses. TheseThese Terms of Use apply solely to NUVO’s Websites. You should always review the terms and conditions of any website that you access through a link from this or any other NUVO Website. E-commerce and Our Secure ServerOur secure server processes commerce transactions with every reasonable effort to insure that your personal information is protected. However, transactions that take place on other sites that have a link from our site are not necessarily handled in this fashion. Consequently, we disclaim any responsibility for transactions conducted on those sites and we cannot vouch for the security of the information submitted in those transactions. ClassifiedsWhen using our classified section(s), understand its terms and agreements: http://indianapolis.nuvo.net/online/classifieds/Terms RSS FeedsNUVO provides the RSS feeds for personal use only, and they may not be modified in any way, posted on any website, or redistributed in any manner unless such use is explicitly agreed upon with NUVO. NUVO reserves the right to object to your use of the RSS feeds and the right to require you to cease using the RSS feeds at any time. NUVO further reserves the right to terminate its distribution of the RSS feeds or change the content or formatting of the RSS feeds at any time without notice to you. NUVO provides this content "as is" and NUVO shall not be held liable for your use of the information or the feeds. By accessing the RSS feeds, you indicate that you understand and agree to these terms and conditions. IndemnityYou agree to indemnify and hold harmless NUVO and its affiliates, and each of their respective employees, officers, directors, owners, licensees, licensors and agents, from any and all claims, liabilities, costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees and court costs, arising out of or related to any allegation regarding (a) any violation of these Terms of Use by you, (b) your use of this Website, including but not limited to the placement or transmission of any content or information on this Website, or (c) the use by NUVO or any of its affiliates of any content or information you provide, as long as our use is not inconsistent with these Terms of Use. Limitation of LiabilityNUVO WILL NOT BE HELD LIABLE, UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCE, FOR YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ABOUT THE INFORMATION AND MATERIALS APPEARING ON THIS WEBSITE, WHICH ARE PROVIDED "AS IS." NUVO MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THIS WEBSITE AT ANY TIME INCLUDING CHANGES TO THESE TERMS OF USE. NUVO DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND ANY WARRANTY REGARDING THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS OR TIMELINESS OF THE CONTENT, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, LINKS OR OTHER ITEMS CONAINED HEREIN. NUVO DOES NOT MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS THAT THIS WEBSITE OR ITS CONTENTS WILL BE ERROR FREE OR THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED OR THAT THIS WEBSITE SHALL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMLESS COMPONENTS. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE, SHALL NUVO BE HELD LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR EXPENSES WHATSOEVER ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR FOR ANY MATERIALS CONTAINED HEREIN, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT NUVO IS NOT LIABLE FOR ANY CONDUCT OF ANY USER.This Website may contain views, opinions and statements of various third party individuals and organizations on the Website. NUVO neither endorses nor makes any representation or warranty whatsoever regarding the views, opinions or statements provided by any third party or any user of this Website. It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness and usefulness of any information, opinion or contents available through the Website and to seek appropriate advice of professionals, as appropriate. NUVO has not reviewed and does not endorse the content of all sites linked to from this Website and your linking to any third party website is at your sole risk. Sale of CompanyIn the event of a sale, the email database and all user information shall accrue to the new owners of NUVO. However, your personally identifiable information will continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. JurisdictionSince our Site is published in the United States, U.S. law shall govern any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise. This agreement shall also be governed by the laws of the State of Indiana, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. You and NUVO each agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Indiana. If any provision of this agreement shall be considered unlawful or void or is unenforceable in whole or in part, the remaining provisions shall remain in full force and effect. This Agreement and any operating rules established by NUVO for any community areas on the Website constitute the entire agreement between the parties and supersede all previous written or oral agreements between the parties with respect to the subject matter. No waiver by either party of any breach or default hereunder shall be deemed to be a waiver of any proceeding or subsequent breach or default. Copyright ClaimsNUVO prohibits the posting of any information or materials that violates or infringes the copyrights of any person or entity. If you believe that your work has been copied and made available on this Website in a manner that would constitute copyright infringement, provide the following information in writing:an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other intellectual propertya description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed;a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Website;your address, telephone number, and email address;a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and,a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner's behalf.Send your notice of claims of copyright or other intellectual property infringement: By mail:Copyright AgentNUVO, Inc.3951 N. Meridian St.Indianapolis, IN 46208 By email:editors@nuvo.net Upon receipt of such notification, NUVO will remove any posted submission found to be infringing the rights of any person or entity in conformance with 17 U.S.C. §512(c)(3). United States law provides strict penalties for submitting false claims of infringement.
Trending Now
Mayberry Magic
Big Car Collaborative: Not driving on empty during the pandemic
Face it, the KKK was us, not him: A Hoosier reckoning
It’s about time you knew about townships
Indiana attorneys general support lawsuits challenging Biden’s election
EVENTS
43°
Clear
Indianapolis, IN
(46208)
Today
A mix of clouds and sun in the morning followed by cloudy skies during the afternoon. High 59F. Winds S at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
Periods of rain. Low 51F. Winds S at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 90%. Rainfall near a half an inch.
Updated: December 11, 2020 @ 12:41 am
Full Forecast
Support Local Journalism
Thank you for your donation, 100% of which goes to our writers
JOIN
The NUVO Cultural Foundation is a 501(c)3 nonprofit
© Copyright 2020 NUVO, 3951 N. Meridian St., Suite 200 Indianapolis, IN | Terms of Use / Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
